<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Inaho.label>Inaho</Inaho.label>
  <Inaho.description>Can be turned into White rice in five steps:\n1. Threshing. Threshing converts the Inaho into Momi and straw.\n 2. Separating. Colonists can split the Momi into Brown rice and Rice Husk.\n 3. Polishing. By polishing Brown rice, colonists can get White rice and rice bran.\n 4. Cooking. Colonists can decide how to include White rice in their meals.\n 5. Eating. Through tasting the bounty of their work, colonists will appreciate the flavor immensely.</Inaho.description>

  <Inaho_Mochi.label>Inaho (GR)</Inaho_Mochi.label>
  <Inaho_Mochi.description>Can be turned into Glutinous rice in four steps:\n1. Threshing. Threshing converts the Inaho (GR) into Momi (GR) and straw.\n 2. Separating. Colonists can split the Momi (GR) into Glutinous rice and Rice Husk \n 3.Cooking. Colonists can decide how to include Glutinous rice in their meals.4. Through tasting the bounty of their work, colonists will appreciate the flavor immensely.</Inaho_Mochi.description>

  <RiceMomi.label>Momi</RiceMomi.label>
  <RiceMomi.description>Rice still in its shell. Cannot be eaten.\nBy threshing, colonists can get Brown rice and straw.</RiceMomi.description>

  <RiceMomi_Mochi.label>Momi (GR)</RiceMomi_Mochi.label>
  <RiceMomi_Mochi.description>Rice still in its shell. Cannot be eaten.\nBy threshing, colonists can get Glutinous rice and straw.</RiceMomi_Mochi.description>


  <Straw.label>Straw</Straw.label>
  <Straw.description>A by-product of threshing Rice Plant.\nIt is useful in various endeavors, such as animal feed, fertilizer, fuel, or crafts.</Straw.description>

  <Chaff.label>Rice Husk</Chaff.label>
  <Chaff.description>A by-product of separating Paddy.\n It is useful in various endeavors, such as low nutrition animal feed, fertilizer, or fuel.</Chaff.description>

  <RiceBran.label>Rice bran</RiceBran.label>
  <RiceBran.description>A by-product of polishing Brown rice.\n Once processed, it can be used for fertilizer, animal feed, or preserved meals.</RiceBran.description>

  <RiceByproduct.label>By-products bag</RiceByproduct.label>
  <RiceByproduct.description>A bag full of by-products of rice. It can be processed into compost and animal feed.\nThis eases the colony's storage; moreover, colonists can choose to unpack both Rice Husk and rice bran from a bag, or extract one and dispose of the other.</RiceByproduct.description>

</LanguageData>